Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: PTS Conference Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 163, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.3:no.2
  - Item 11: You too can go into business, Publication (Box 163, Folder 3)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Imports HURT!, 1971; Publication (Box 163, Folder 4)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Salaried Sparks, 1956-1957 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-11
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: PTS Conference Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 163, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-2, 5, 7- 8
  - Item 2: PTS Conference Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 163, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1- 6
  - Item 3: PTS Conference Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 163, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1
  - Item 4: PTS Conference Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 163, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1- 2
  - Item 5: PTS Conference Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 163, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1- 2
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: IUE handbook for local union officers, Publication (Box 163, Folder 7)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Report, 1966; Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.4- 12
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining Report, 1967; Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 1- 12
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Report, 1968; Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 1-6, 8- 12
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Report, 1969; Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 1- 12
  - Item 5: Collective Bargaining Report, 1970; Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 1, 3-7, 9-12
  - Item 6: Collective Bargaining Report, 1971; Publication (Box 163, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 1- 11
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Professional - Technical - Salaried, Handbook of Selected Contract Clauses, Publication (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Research Department Report, 1977; Publication (Box 163, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 11 (1977)
  - Item 3: The Developing Crisis in Electronics and Companion Industries, 1969; Publication (Box 163, Folder 9)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Salaried Sparks, 1955; Publication (Box 163, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1,3-4,7-11 (1955)
  - Item 2: Salaried Sparks, 1956; Publication (Box 163, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.1,3 (1956)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A chronology of Ice's Social Action Programs, 1971; Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: A report on the IUE Young Workers' Institute: Boston, Massachusetts, June 1971, Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: How to handle a grievance, 1972; Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: IUE AFL-CIO Pension Fund: summary plan description as amended, January 1, 1976, Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Questions about the IUE, 1972; Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Social Action, 1973; Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol. 4, no.5-6 (1973)
  - Item 7: Social Action, 1975; Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 3 (1975)
  - Item 8: Women in the IUE, 1969; Publication (Box 163, Folder 11)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Technician Topics, 1969; Publication (Box 163, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 2-4 (1969)
  - Item 2: Technician Topics, 1970; Publication (Box 163, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 2 (1970)
  - Item 3: Technician Topics, 1971; Publication (Box 163, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol. 3, no.1 (1971)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Westinghouse Picket, 1955; Publication (Box 163, Folder 13)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.1-9 (1955)
  - Item 2: Westinghouse Picket, 1956; Publication (Box 163, Folder 13)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-5 (1956)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Spotlight focuses on Westinghouse, Publication (Box 163, Folder 14)
- Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers, Publication (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Handbook for union Shop Stewards, 1976; Publication (Box 163, Folder 15)
    Author: Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: At the world labor conference, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
    Author: Albert J. Fitzgerald
  - Item 2: Good Advice!, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Greetings, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Highlights of the Joint Job Evaluation Plan, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1945 May 18
  - Item 5: How corporations conceal profits and how to understand your corporation's financial report, 1943; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: How the UE was formed, Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Report of the general officers, 1939; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The shop steward on the job: how to settle grievances, enforce the contract, build the union, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The shop steward on the job: how to settle grievances, enforce the contract, build the union, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The UE shop steward: how to settle grievances, enforce the contract, build the union, 1948; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The UE shop steward: how to settle grievances, enforce the contract, build the union, 1947; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: U.E. guide to wage payment plans, time study, and job evaluation, 1943; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: U.E. manual on Executive Order 9240, 1943; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: UE fights for job security: a union program for higher wages and jobs, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: UE guide for Servicemen's and Veterans' Welfare Committees, Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: UE guide to political action, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: UE-CIO looks at FDR., 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Victory, peace, and jobs, 1943-1944 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    Author: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. General Officers
    Notes: Report of General Officers. Copy 4
  - Item 19: When you come back, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 1)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A little bit of UE history you should know, 1968; Publication (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: All of us built America, 1968; Publication (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The decline of the AFL-CIO, 1962; Publication (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Vietnam, the inside story, 1968; Publication (Box 164, Folder 2)
    Author: Schoenbrun, David
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Contributory Annuity plan as agreed to between F.E. and U.E. and the International Harvester Company, 1950; Publication (Box 164, Folder 3)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Plan of group insurance for our employees, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Author: Sheridan Machine Co.
  - Item 2: A Plan of group insurance for our employees, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Author: Dictograph Sales Corporation
  - Item 3: A Plan of group insurance for our employees, 1945; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Author: Newark Transformer Company
  - Item 4: A Plan of group insurance for our employees, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Author: Espey Mfg. Co., Inc.
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Plan, 1947; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Author: Gardner Electric Manufacturing Company, Inc.
  - Item 6: New Group Insurance Plan, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Author: Travelers Insurance Company
  - Item 7: UE guide to group insurance, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: UE shows the way on pensions and insurance!, 1950; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: UE Your group insurance plan, 1947; Publication (Box 164, Folder 4)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: In the matter of the Arbitration between United Electrical and RCA Victor Division of Radio Corporation of America, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 5)
    Notes: Award and Opinion
  - Item 2: Watson Elevator Co., and the United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local 447, 1946; Publication (Box 164, Folder 5)
- United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare., Publication (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Communist domination of unions and national security, 1952; Publication (Box 164, Folder 6)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare.
    Notes: Copy 4
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Alliance for survival: the fight for decent working conditions and the fight for a decent environment, 1972; Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
    Author: Barry Commoner
  - Item 2: How foreign is "foreign" competition, 1970; Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Safeguarding the union's integrity, remarks by James J. Matles., 1973; Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
    Author: James J. Matles
  - Item 4: Survey - Women in the development of America, 1939; Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Thirst for learning: ... a lifetime need, 1973; Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
    Author: Lillie Pope
  - Item 6: Together we win: the fight for equality on the job, 1973; Publication (Box 164, Folder 7)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: UE guide to group insurance, 1944; Publication (Box 164, Folder 8)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Catholic GE Workers speak out for UE (an open letter to GE workers of all faiths), Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1947; Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1950; Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Correspondence, 1952; Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Electrical Union News - April 28, 1950, Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Forewarned is forearmed, Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: GE Vets speak out on the NLRB election, Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Summary of UE-GE Settlement as it affects Local 301, 1953; Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Tool-Die-Craftsmen Conference., 1952; Publication (Box 164, Folder 9)
    Notes: 1952 May 25
  - Item 10: UER & MWA - Local 301 - Gifts made (years 1948-1949) (Box 164, Folder 9)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Remington Rand, Inc. is wrong, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
    Notes: Memo
  - Item 2: Report of Committee to membership and action taken at meeting, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Report on the trial against Remington Rand, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: A timely suggestion, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: A timely suggestion!, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Are you bucking for a promotion..., Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Are you making nine times as much, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Are you making nine times as much?, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Emergency meeting tomorrow, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Emergency meeting tomorrow, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Report on the trial against Remington Rand, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: UE calls on Rand to stop stalling, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: UE calls on Rand to stop stalling, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Union takes action against Remington Rand, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Union takes action against Remington Rand, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: A report on emergency membership meetings, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: A report on emergency membership meetings held March 31, 1948, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Are you bucking for a promotion, Mr. Baker, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Company-AFL move Blocked, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Rem Rand found guilty, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Remington Rand lets the cat out of the bag, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Remington Rand stands alone again, Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Rem-Rand Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 164, Folder 10)
    Notes: 1948 May 25
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Strike Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 164, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.4-15, 17-25
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Range keeper, 1948; Publication (Box 164, Folder 12)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Local supplement to agreement between Westinghouse Electric Corporation and United electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1950; Publication (Box 164, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Meter Reader, 1953; Publication (Box 164, Folder 13)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-4,6 (1953)
  - Item 3: This is your UE Local 426 Supplement, Publication (Box 164, Folder 13)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A frau exposed!, Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Conference on women in the electrical radio & machine industry, 1941; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Protect your wages: fight for price rollbacks price control, 1943; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Research Bulletin, 1948; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Steward's Guide on the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Summary of proceedings - Women's conference., 1949; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: The fight for jobs: U.E. District Four officers report for 1944-45., 1944-1945 (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: The Fight for women workers' rights - a factual survey, 1952; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Women's rights - (resolution on ), 1951; Publication (Box 164, Folder 14)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: UE 1936-1944 - Published by District 4, 10th International Convention, Hotel New YorkerSept. 25-29, 1944, Publication (Box 164, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: We fought for our union!: the story of the Univis strike, 1948; Publication (Box 164, Folder 15)
    Author: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 7
  - Item 3: We took our fight to the people, 1947; Publication (Box 164, Folder 15)
    Author: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 4
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Front, 1946; Publication (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.5:no.6-7
  - Item 2: Labor Front, 1947; Publication (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-4, 6-7
  - Item 3: Labor Front, 1948; Publication (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1-3, 4-6
  - Item 4: Labor Front, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.8:no.1-3
  - Item 5: UE Record, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.8:no.4-7
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: USA before the NLRB - In the matter of National Electric Products Corporation and United Electrical and Radio Workers of America, Local No. 609, 1937; Publication (Box 165, Folder 2)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Lets go to press!, Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Report of the general officers - serial, 1938; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: UE Legislative Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
    Notes: no. 9
  - Item 4: UE Legislative and Political Action Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: UE Legislative and Political Action Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: UE Report on Congress - The First hundred days of the 81st Congress, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Your union at work, 1940; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Your union at work, 1941; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Your union at work, 1941; Publication (Box 165, Folder 3)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Shop News, 1947; Publication (Box 165, Folder 4)
    Author: UERMWA, CIO, Local 450
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-12
  - Item 2: Shop News, 1948; Publication (Box 165, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1-11
  - Item 3: Shop News, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.8:no.1,3-9
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Shop News, 1942-1945 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    Notes: 3rd Anniv. Issue
  - Item 2: Technicians survey, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Facts about your contract, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Is P.R. Democratic?, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Local prepares to fight, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Taft-Hartley Law in Action, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: What? When? How? Who? Where? P.R., Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: What's wrong?, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Engineers, Economics and Security, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Executive Board Meeting Local 450, 1948; Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Local 450 - Press Release, 1955; Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Let's look at the record, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Minutes - Stewards Council, 1948; Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Overtime Rotation, Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: PAC Steard's Notes #2, 1947; Publication (Box 165, Folder 5)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: CIO Daily Bulletin, 1937; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Here is your union: the story of UE 430, 1952; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Author: Henry Kraus
  - Item 3: Newark Evening News, 1949; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Side by side, Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Speed up Threatens - Our jobs - Our lives, 1956; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The first official UE meeting of Local 328, 1963; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Light, 1953; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1
  - Item 8: Transmitter, 1948; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.5:no.5
  - Item 9: UE 768 News, 1951; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1951 March
  - Item 10: UE Local 437 News, 1953; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1:no.3
  - Item 11: UE, Local 324, Binghamton, NY -- Report, 1944; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: UE, Local 324, Binghamton, NY -- Report, 1946; Publication (Box 165, Folder 6)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A message to you from UE, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Greetings..., Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: How the UE was formed, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: How UE can help you win a more secure future!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Organizing for security, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Support UE workers in their fight for a living wage!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: UE presents Leland Stowe, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: UE women face the future, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Why high food prices?, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: You and your Steward!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Your UE news, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Leaflets on "Your union at work", Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
    Notes: no. 1-3, 6, 8-9
  - Item 13: Stop the drive to war!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Telling the town!: UE guide for community action: how to prepare and issue news releases, write newspaper advertisements, radio broadcasts, etc., 1946; Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: UE fights for job security, 1945; Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: UE-These are the questions 42,000 other salaried people have asked, Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Vets can't eat medals, 1946; Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
    Author: Linfield, Seymour
  - Item 18: When you come back: UE's orientation handbook for returning servicemen, 1945; Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Your union at work, 1946; Publication (Box 166, Folder 1)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A message to salaried employees from UE, Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Support UE Workers in their fight for a living wage!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: UE fights for a better America!, 1946; Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: UE guide to political action, 1944; Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: UE these the questions 42,000 other salaried people have asked, Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: UE, the members run this union!: an answer to the Saturday Evening Post, 1947; Publication (Box 166, Folder 2)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 10 to 1, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 5[cents] a day, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Chug-Chug, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Keep America at work!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Let them eat beans!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Profits up prices up, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: They saidprices would come down!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: UE means teamwork, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Who's got the money?, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: You are in danger!, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Correspondence from UE, 1947; Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Investigation of Communist infiltration of UERMWA, 1948; Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
    Author: United States. Congress. House. Committee on Education and Labor
  - Item 13: Monopoly, Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Peace on Earth, 1947; Publication (Box 166, Folder 3)